My clone again — in English, because I don't speak Mandarin, and that's part of the point. If you're thinking of using the free engine for Mandarin narration, here are all eight voices. One honest thing first: the pack grades every one of these a D — its own report card, its own words, non-English support is thinner. You should hear what a D sounds like before you build with it. Each voice says its name and the house line: the machine brings the hands — you bring the taste. Cast by ear.
我是小北，普通话女声。
机器带来双手，品味由你决定。
[I'm Xiaobei, Mandarin female. The machine brings the hands — you bring the taste.]
我是小妮，普通话女声。
机器带来双手，品味由你决定。
[I'm Xiaoni, Mandarin female. The machine brings the hands — you bring the taste.]
我是小小，普通话女声。
机器带来双手，品味由你决定。
[I'm Xiaoxiao, Mandarin female. The machine brings the hands — you bring the taste.]
我是小艺，普通话女声。
机器带来双手，品味由你决定。
[I'm Xiaoyi, Mandarin female. The machine brings the hands — you bring the taste.]
我是云健，普通话男声。
机器带来双手，品味由你决定。
[I'm Yunjian, Mandarin male. The machine brings the hands — you bring the taste.]
我是云希，普通话男声。
机器带来双手，品味由你决定。
[I'm Yunxi, Mandarin male. The machine brings the hands — you bring the taste.]
我是云夏，普通话男声。
机器带来双手，品味由你决定。
[I'm Yunxia, Mandarin male. The machine brings the hands — you bring the taste.]
我是云扬，普通话男声。
机器带来双手，品味由你决定。
[I'm Yunyang, Mandarin male. The machine brings the hands — you bring the taste.]
我是小小，普通话女声。
机器带来双手，品味由你决定。
[I'm Xiaoxiao, Mandarin female. The machine brings the hands — you bring the taste.]